(Sheldon:)She's smart, insightful.
(Sheldon:)She has a very unique way of,
you know, revering me.
- Here's your spinach-mushroom omelet.
- Thank you.
(Sheldon:)- Did anyone touch it?
- Gloves were worn by everyone involved.
(Ramona:)I was vigilant.
(Sheldon:)Ramona pointed out
that I've been wasting 20 minutes a day...
(Sheldon:)...standing on cafeteria lines.
(Ramona:)Time which would be better spent tackling
the great physics problems of our day.
(Sheldon:)You don't tackle the big issues, Ramona.
You fence with them. En garde. Riposte.
[LAUGH ING]
Touché.
(Leonard:)- Morning.
- Oh, hey, Leslie.
So I see you're organizing your papers...
(Leslie:)...for the Smithsonian Museum
of Dumb-Assery.
(Ramona:)There won't be any room until they get rid
of the permanent Leslie Winkle exhibit.
(Sheldon:)Oh, good one.
(Leslie:)I see you got a grad student
to fight your battles.
(Leslie:)I'll let you keep your lunch money today.